https://www.ectnews.com/about/privacy.xhtml

ECT News Network > Privacy Policy
We're open for business and ready to work with you during the COVID-19 outbreak.
ECT News Network Privacy Policy
Updated December 27, 2019
Overview
This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use
it, and how to modify or correct it. The policies set forth below are
applicable to the online media properties and electronic newsletters
(collectively referred to herein as "the Service") which
are owned and operated by ECT News Network, Inc.
Privacy Mission
ECT News Network is a privacy conscious organization and we are strongly
committed to your right to privacy. Because we gather certain types
of information about our users, we want to help you understand the
terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that
information.
Data Collection
ECT News Network collects personal information from users during registration,
and in certain areas of the Service where visitors provide
information together with content submissions, postings to online
community discussion boards, suggestions, surveys, voting and opinion
polling. ECT News Network uses this information for its internal
objectives, including but not limited to editorial and feedback
purposes. You may be able to access and view portions of the Service
without providing personal information, but other areas may require
registration for access.
ECT News Network may collect non-personal information, such as
information obtained from other sources, or aggregated information
that does not identify individual customers.
We may also collect the
domains and IP addresses of visitors to the Service, as well as
information such as browser type and operating system that is
generally transmitted by your browser.
Use of Your Information
Information submitted at the time of registration or content submission may be
used for marketing and promotional purposes by ECT News Network.
We
may also collect and use information about how our users use the
Service, including search terms entered, pages visited and documents
viewed.
This information is unique-number identifiable, and is used
for purposes of enabling us to provide you with a personalized user
experience. Aggregated forms of this data may also be used in order
to help us understand areas for future research and to identify
future features and functions to develop for the Service. This data
may also be used by the Service to identify appropriate product
offerings and subscription plans.
The Service and its partners may also use your information:
To respond to an inquiry or request for information;
To thank you for contacting the Service;
To welcome you to the Service and to its products and services;
To explain new product offerings and features of our services;
To notify you of special promotions;
To attribute content you make available through the Service;
To communicate with you regarding customer service related issues;
For the purposes for which you provided the information; and
To enforce the legal terms that govern your use of the Service, including this privacy policy and our
Terms of Service.
Registration
In order to use some features of the Service and to participate in interactive
sessions, you will be asked to complete a registration form. During
registration, you may be required to provide contact information for
yourself and the company you represent -- as well as business
information about the company you represent. ECT News Network may use
this contact information as a means of confirmation of your identity,
position, or relationship to a particular enterprise or company. By
using the Service, you agree to reveal only information that you are
authorized to disclose and know to be true. During interactive
sessions, we may also collect your opinions and preferences regarding
certain products or services. We use this information to provide you
with quality services as well as with offers that we think are
relevant to you based on the preferences you share at registration or
during interactive sessions. Please see the Information Sharing and
Disclosure section below.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
ECT News Network may share certain aggregated demographic information
with our sponsors regarding the users of the Service and responses we
receive from you via interactive sessions. The aggregated information
that we provide does not contain any personally identifiable
information.
ECT News Network may provide authorized access to personal
information to employees and others who assist us in providing the
Service.
In addition, ECT News Network may share personal
information with companies that have been approved by ECT News
Network so that they can provide you with information about goods and
services we believe might interest you. You can opt out of such
sharing by e-mail
request or by modifying your registration information
online.
If you have accessed the Service via the Web site of one of our
partners, then any information that you provide is provided both to
us and to the partner. The partner's use of this information is
governed by the partner's privacy policy. You should contact these
partners directly if you have any questions about their use of the
information.
ECT News Network may disclose your personal information if we believe
it is necessary to share information in order to investigate,
prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected
fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety
of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise
required by law.
In the event ECT News Network is acquired by or merged with another
company, we may transfer your information as part of the business
transaction.
Special Offers
As a registered user, and based upon the preferences you chose at registration, you
will occasionally receive information on products, services, special
offers and newsletters. Out of respect for your privacy, we present
the option
to not receive these types of communications. As part of our services,
we may contact you with offers, promotions and information on interactive sessions
sponsored by identified third parties. All of the content related to such
correspondence is provided by our sponsors, and ECT News Network
disclaims any liability for such content. By virtue of their
sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable
information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in
promotions. By participating in such promotions, you agree to provide
these third parties with your personal information, and further agree
that their use of the information is subject to those parties’
own privacy policies.
In the event you submit your information in
response to a contest or offer provided by ECT News Network in
conjunction with one of our partners, that information is provided
both to ECT News Network and the partner.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive that may contain information
about you and your use of the Service.
ECT News Network utilizes
cookies to identify you and your access privileges when using the
Service. We also may use cookies to enhance and track usage, and
better understand how the Service is used.
Cookies do not contain
your personally identifiable information.
Users of the Service may occasionally get cookies from our
advertisers. These cookies are set by the advertisers and are subject
to those advertisers’ policies. By using the Service, you
expressly agree that the ECT News Network bears no liability
whatsoever, for real or perceived privacy invasion, or usage tracking
technologies used by third-party ad services which are utilized by
various advertisers. You agree that ECT News Network has no control
over content served by third-party ad services, and that any remedies
must be sought solely against those services.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you
can set your browser to refuse cookies. The "Help" section
of the toolbar on most browsers will describe how to stop accepting
new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and
how to disable existing cookies. However, if you do not accept
cookies from a domain owned by ECT News Network, it is possible that
the Service will not function properly for you at all times.
Links to Other Web Sites
ECT News Network may provide links to other Web sites for your
convenience and information. ECT News Network is not responsible for
the privacy procedures of these other sites. The entities that
operate these sites are responsible for the content of their sites,
any products or services they may offer through their sites, or any
other use of their sites. Other Web sites may have their own privacy
notices in place, which we recommend you review if you visit them as
a result of your use of the Service.
Security
ECT News Network maintains reasonable administrative, technical and physical
safeguards to defend against unauthorized disclosure, use, alteration
or destruction of the personal information in our possession.
Your California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident, you are entitled by law to request an
Information Sharing Disclosure.
If you provide notice to the address
below, ECT News Network will provide you with a notice of your right
to prevent sharing of your personal information as well as a
cost-free means of doing so.
To receive such a notice, submit a
written request to our Reader Services Department, specifying that you seek
your "California Customer Choice Notice."
Please allow
30 days for response.
California Consumer Protection Act (CCPA) | Opt-Out Request
If you are a California resident, you have the right to direct us to not sell your personal information to third parties by filing an "Opt-Out Request." If you do not wish for us to sell your personal information to third parties, please use our online form to submit your request. Your request should include your First Name, Last Name, Street Address, City, State, Zip Code, Email Address and Phone Number. When we receive your request, ECT News Network, Inc. will review your submission and begin searching our database for personal information that may be held about you. To verify your submission we will attempt to match the data you provide with any data that we may have stored in our systems. You can expect a response to your request within 45 days of your form submission.
Visiting Our Websites from Outside the United States
This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our websites from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy.
Privacy of Children
ECT News Network and the Services it provides are not directed to children
under the age of 13. The Service operates in compliance with the
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and we do not knowingly
accept registration by, and will not intentionally collect or use
personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of
age. In the event that we learn that we have collected any personal
information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of
parental consent, we will delete that information from our database.
How to Change User InformationYou
may update or correct information you previously provided to ECT News
Network by accessing your user
profile. If you have any questions or concerns about the
ECT News Network privacy policy or would like the personally
identifiable information that you have provided to ECT News Network
removed from our files, please contact
us.
Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy
We may change or update portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and
without prior notice to you. We suggest that you check this page
periodically so you are aware of any policy changes or updates. We
will indicate above the effective date of the update or change.
Governing Law
This policy and the use of this Service are governed by California law.
Any claim
related to the Service or this policy shall be brought in a federal
or state court in Los Angeles County, California, within one year
after the claim arises.
You consent to the jurisdiction and venue of
such court as the most convenient and appropriate for the resolution
of disputes concerning this policy.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding this privacy policy,
please contact us at:
Attn:
Reader Services
ECT News Network, Inc.
Copyright 1998-2020 ECT News Network, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
